export const Doubt=[
    {

        question:"Acceleration due to Gravity Definition ",
        answer:"The acceleration with which a body falls towards the earth due to earths gravitational pull is known as acceleration due to gravity. It is denoted by g",
        subject:"Physics (12)",
        date:"18/09/23",
        author:"Akash Sharma"
    },
    {

        question:"Buoyancy & Buoyant Forces Formulas And Definitions",
        answer:"When a body is put in a fluid, it experiences an upward force. A cork pushed under water soon rises upward. Similarly, a balloon filled with hydrogen rises in the atmosphere. Substances appear lighter when immersed wholly or partially in a liquid. The tendency of a fluid to exert an upward force on an object immersed wholly or partially in the fluid is called  buoyancy. The upward thrust that acts on an object immersed in a fluid is called buoyant force.",
        subject:"Physics (12)",
        date:"18/09/23",
        author:"Akash Sharma"
    },
    {
        question:"Application Of First Law Of Thermodynamicsn ",
        answer:"Consider a system that consists of a gas enclosed by a piston in a cylinder. Suppose the system is taken quasistatically from an initial state Pi, Vi, Ti to a final state Pf, Vf, Tf. At each step the work done and heat exchanged are measured. We know that both the total work done W and the total heat transfer Q to or from the system depend on the thermodynamic path. However, the difference Q - W, is the same for all paths between the given initial and final equilibrium states, and it is equal to the change in internal energy DELTA U of the system.U = Q - W .  In  the above statement, Q is positive when heat enters the system and W is positive when work is done by the system on its surroundings.  "
,        subject:"Physics (12)",
        date:"18/19/23",
        author:"Akash Sharma"
    },
    {
        question:"Could electronic devices charge themselves without being plugged into an electricity source?",
        answer:"The acceleration with which a body falls towards the earth due to earth"
  ,      subject:"Physics (12)",
        date:"18/09123",
        author:"Akash Sharma"
    },
    {
        question:"Acceleration due to Gravity Definition ",
        answer:"The acceleration with which a body falls towards the earth due to eart"
  ,     subject:"Physics (12)",
        date:"18/09123",
        author:"Akash Sharma"
    },
    {
        question:"Acceleration due to Gravity Definition ",
        answer:"The acceleration with which a body falls towards the earth due to eart"
  ,      subject:"Physics (12)",
        date:"18/09123",
        author:"Akash Sharma"
    },

]
export const PDoubt=[
    {

        question:"Acceleration due to Gravity Definition ",
        answer:"The acceleration with which a body falls towards the earth due to earths gravitational pull is known as acceleration due to gravity. It is denoted by g",
        subject:"Physics (11)",
        date:"18/09/23",
        author:"Rahul Sharma"
    },
    {

        question:"Buoyancy & Buoyant Forces Formulas And Definitions",
        answer:"When a body is put in a fluid, it experiences an upward force. A cork pushed under water soon rises upward. Similarly, a balloon filled with hydrogen rises in the atmosphere. Substances appear lighter when immersed wholly or partially in a liquid. The tendency of a fluid to exert an upward force on an object immersed wholly or partially in the fluid is called  buoyancy. The upward thrust that acts on an object immersed in a fluid is called buoyant force.",
        subject:"Physics (12)",
        date:"18/09/23",
        author:"Akash Singh"
    },
    {
        question:"Could electronic devices charge themselves without being plugged into an electricity source?",
        answer:"Consider a system that consists of a gas enclosed by a piston in a cylinder. Suppose the system is taken quasistatically from an initial state Pi, Vi, Ti to a final state Pf, Vf, Tf. At each step the work done and heat exchanged are measured. We know that both the total work done W and the total heat transfer Q to or from the system depend on the thermodynamic path. However, the difference Q - W, is the same for all paths between the given initial and final equilibrium states, and it is equal to the change in internal energy DELTA U of the system.U = Q - W .  In  the above statement, Q is positive when heat enters the system and W is positive when work is done by the system on its surroundings.  "
,        subject:"Physics (12)",
        date:"18/19/23",
        author:"subham Banerjee"
    },
    {
        question:"Could electronic devices charge themselves without being plugged into an electricity source?",
        answer:"The acceleration with which a body falls towards the earth due to earth"
  ,      subject:"Physics (10)",
        date:"18/09123",
        author:"Akash Sharma"
    },
    {
        question:" An object dropped from a cliff falls with a constant acceleration of 10 m/s2. Find its speed 5 s after it was dropped. ",
        answer:"The acceleration with which a body falls towards the earth due to eart"
  ,     subject:"Physics (10)",
        date:"18/09123",
        author:"Akash Sharma"
    },
    {
        question:"A bullet hits a Sandbox with a velocity of 20 m/s and penetrates it up to a distance of 6 cm. Find the deceleration of the bullet in the sandbox.",
        answer:"The acceleration with which a body falls towards the earth due to eart"
  ,      subject:"Physics (12)",
        date:"18/09123",
        author:"Akash Sharma"
    },

]